Hello Culerada! Hello Zerfistas!
The match just ended.
-1 by a miracle.
Last second.
Penalty.
A totally undeserved result,
totally unfair.
One of the worst matches of the Flick era,
by a long shot.
I include Flick in this disaster.
In fact,
I hold him quite responsible because I don't
know what the fuck he was trying to do.
I don't know if a 0-0 was good enough for us.
I don't know if even a 1-0 was good enough because
it's not like they scored the 1-0 on us.
I mean,
you could say that we've
been very lucky.
Very lucky also because they are an
opponent that is not top 10 in the Champions League,
not by a long shot.
We already know,
you can understand the first
half because you say,
well,
they've won every duel against us,
but in the second half
they won every duel against us.
We've done the thing with the cleats again.
I don't know.
A billion-dollar budget.
Isn't there someone there to say,
look,
wear these cleats because otherwise you're going
to slip, because it's been happening for many matches.
In the end, I'm going to
think they're idiots,
man.
I just don't see any other explanation.
How can you be
slipping all the time
when the guys from the other
team are not slipping?
I don't get it, really.
You come off the bench
and the first thing you do
is slip three times
as if you were a
newborn fawn.
I'm Bambi, I was just born.
Man, what about the others?
Fuck, that guy's physique was unreal.
He didn't stop.
Tonali, Joelinton.
Fuck,
and as for us, they've
won every duel against us.
Physically we are very,
very,
very bad and we got knocked out of
Europe and we saw it.
In the Spanish league, they don't see anything
because all the teams are
a piece of shit on a stick.
But you go there and they beat you in
absolutely every duel.
Every single one.
Every one.
Well, that's it.
We started with Araujo
because Eric wasn't there.
I see it now.
I forgot to
put on my headphones.
Araujo as a right-back,
which, in principle,
was a plan that I liked, and well.
But really, no.
They've attacked a lot
down the left.
They've attacked much more down the right.
But
in attack, I don't know if
he had orders not to push up.
Then at the end he was there, I don't
know if injured or with cramps
and he didn't track back, and that's
when they scored the goal on us.
On a cross where they
easily got away
there on Cancelo's flank.
I don't know.
But oh well.
They've shot I don't know how many times.
They've been hovering around.
They took 100 corners.
I don't know.
The thing is, from the first half, you can take away
the thought that, well, it was a serious match.
The second half was just pathetic.
It was pathetic.
It was a shame.
In the Patreons group,
someone said that
the players and the coaching
staff should pay the money
for the away trip back to those who
went to see the match.
Man. By the way.
By the way.
My friend Guillem told me.
And the same thing happened to me.
They didn't announce it.
I mean.
They put them on sale on a Friday and on
Sunday they already stopped
selling them and they didn't even announce
that you could buy the
tickets for the away match.
That's how much Barça cares.
Because, of course.
There are no commissions there.
Not in away ticket sales.
So they don't give a damn.
They didn't even sell all
the tickets that were available.
They didn't even announce it.
They didn't even bother.
Well.
That's it.
Pathetic match.
I mean.
Rafinha today.
The second-season Rafinha.
I mean.
He didn't get a single thing right.
In the end, he made one play.
I mean.
He passed to Lewandowski, who missed.
Lewandowski.
I mean.
Pathetic.
Simple as that.
Pathetic match.
One more.
And then the other guy comes out saying that
we have to renew his contract to thank him.
To thank him? What do we have to
thank Lewandowski for?
What do we have to thank him for?
What favors has he done for us?
Fucking Lewandowski.
What favors has he done for us.
Earning 32 million a year.
That's the favor he's done for us.
He did us a favor by coming to Barça.
Lewandowski.
Or what?
For fuck's sake.
What favor has
Lewandowski done us by coming here.
We paid 50 million to
Bayern and they signed Kane.
No fucking kidding.
And the other guy earning 32 million.
And we still have to do him
the favor of renewing his contract.
Son of a bitch.
How disgusting.
Too many of them.
So disgusting, too many of them.
Very bad today.
Very bad.
We played very badly.
Everyone.
Very bad.
And Flick, very bad too.
He didn't make a fucking change.
I mean.
He subs Pedri.
Bernal is there.
Everyone sees it.
Man. He couldn't move.
We've all been seeing it.
And of the coaching staff, of which there are 80,
nobody sees that Bernal can't move.
And you have to waste a
sub one minute later.
Man. Seriously?
Seriously?
And Lewandowski playing I don't
know how many thousand minutes.
Of course.
I watch Ferran play and I want to gouge my eyes out.
But then I watch Lewandowski
and I miss Ferran.
Very bad.
Very badly played.
And I'm saying this with the draw.
And I hope that here on
Wednesday, with all the fans,
like on the day of the Atleti match,
we play very well and we
score three or four or
five, however many are needed.
But then Atleti will come
and let's see if you beat Atleti.
Playing like this at the Calderón.
And then Arsenal will come
and let's see if you beat Arsenal.
Playing like this at the...
What's it called?
At Highbury.
No. I don't know what the fuck
the Arsenal stadium is called.
If you beat Atleti.
And if you beat Newcastle on Wednesday.
They're exhausted, man.
But why are they so exhausted?
Why are they so exhausted?
Holy shit, man.
We're not playing in that
Club World Cup thing, you know.
Why are they so exhausted?
The hell?
I don't get it.
I just don't get it, damn it.
I don't understand this match today.
It has no explanation for me.
Holy shit.
It's just that I don't...
I don't know, because...
Really, very, very bad.
Very, very bad.
Rafinha was incredibly bad.
Lewandowski is like playing with one man down.
Very bad, man.
Very bad.
Very, very bad.
I don't know.
We have to wait for Gavi to come back.
Let's see if Gavi comes back.
Gavi soon, and someone who can run out there.
I just don't get it.
Even Pedri couldn't
play well.
Fermin was barely seen either,
in the little that Barça did.
Fermin and little else.
I don't know.
I don't get it, man.
Very bad, huh.
Very pissed off.
Very pissed off today.
Well.
On Saturday against Sevilla.
Let's see if I don't...
We get distracted with the
elections and all that shit.
As we already know who's going
to win, of course.
And... And yeah, that's it.
Time to think about Newcastle, the second leg.
But oh well.
Today... Really, very, very disappointed.
Very, very pissed off.
We're out.
Força Barça.
I was forgetting.
I...
I remember one time in EGB, back in those years.
That a teacher told
a classmate of mine.
Look,
when you go to take
a multiple-choice test.
If you think it's A, put B. Well...
With... With Rashford, it's the same thing, man.
He comes on?
It's just every decision he makes.
Is wrong. I mean,
you have to go to the left,
you go to the right.
When you have to go to the right,
you go to the left.
I don't know.
It's like a lot of...
Much ado about nothing.
And... What do I have to pay?
Millions for this guy.
And pay him like a world-class star too.